I can sleep.
This is great!
Imaiki Maki
Cheers!
Maybe...
Saratabiwan Centrair to Akita just now
Seino
Akita
I'm here!
Yay!
We are Se-no!
Super Town, Strong Energy, Positive Exciting Soul from Nakoya!
Team Shach!
The four of us are here in Akita!
This time we are flying from Centrair to Akita!
Do you know what this means?
It means "Come to Akita!
It means "Come to Akita! It's a reaction, like "Come to Akita!
Just "Ke"?
Yes, just "Ke-" Akita!
Yes, so this time I'm going to go to Akita a lot.
I see.
Let's go there!
I want to go to many places.
It took about an hour and a half from Centrair, right?
Surprisingly close!
Amahage welcomes you to Haruko Ineka.
First time for the four of us.
Hey!
They did it!
We'll be there in no time, and the view is great.
I know!
I know.
You know that moment when you're above the clouds?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I love that moment when you go above the clouds.
I want it.
It's a little bit chilly when you get here, right?
Yeah, I'm going to get off.
It's not cool, it's cold.
You know that moment when you get off the plane, you can feel it in the aisle, right?
Yeah, you can tell.
It's like, even though we're in Japan, we're on a trip.
Let's enjoy Akita to the fullest!
Let's put this together and go again.
Let's go again!
Let's go back to Akita from Centrair!
Yes!
Little Kyoto in Michinoku, little Kyoto in Kakuno,
We've come to Kakunoden!
Yes!
Yes, yes!
The samurai residences, with these black walls...
It has a certain atmosphere, doesn't it?
Yes, it does!
It's nice to walk around.
And it's just the right time of year to enjoy the autumn leaves.
Bakkakka!
As you can see, it's really beautiful.
If you come in spring, you'll see cherry blossoms.
In summer, the leaves turn green and blue.
In autumn, you can enjoy the autumn leaves, and in winter, you can enjoy the snowy scenery.
Wow, it's so calm.
Yes.
You can enjoy it any time of the year.
Kakunodate
In Akita
Yes.
Very famous
With creatures.
Yes.
Ha-ha-ha.
I wonder what it is...
But Akita
Creatures
Akita, Akita deer, Akita deer.
Isn't this it?
But that's just a foreshadowing.
Oh, really?
I don't know, maybe it's the color.
Could it be...
What is it, Oguro?
Akita dog.
Mimo...
Yes...
So today...
I'm going to a place called Enishi where you can meet Akita dogs.
I want to go there!
So cute!
Amazing!
Oh, my legs!
My legs!
My feet!
Ew.
Cute.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. He's cute.
Hello, Mommy.
Hello.
Sit, sit, sit.
This is Fujiko-chan. Fujiko-chan.
Look at you, Fujiko-chan.
He's cute, even when he slips a little.
Fujiko-chan, sit.
Oh, and a little foreshadowing.
This is Dinah, Sue-chan.
Sue-chan!
Sue-chan's not here! Sorry.
It's Sue!
What!
You're so quiet, Sue.
No, no, no, no, no.
You're a good girl. You're a really good girl.
He's so cuddly.
You're so cute!
Touch her now.
Get down! Get down!
Get down! Yes!
I got you, Fu-chan!
Waja waja!
You're all right!
Wait a minute! I want to give it to you!
What?
Sit down, Pooh!
You're all over the place when it comes to treats!
You love these treats!
Hey!
Hey, boy!
Eat it!
He's eating so much!
That's great!
Fluffy!
Can you sit down, Fuu?
Oh!
Oh, man! I can sleep!
Oh, no!
He's so cute!
One, two, three!
Oh, my God!
Oh, my gosh!
Saratami one! Centrair color!
Ha-ha-ha!
What a delicious regal ritz I've come to!
Wow!
Mongulan!
Hey!
It's a stylish building!
I'm going to go in right away!
Looking forward to it!
Yes!
There's a black mongolian called "Bukeya-style mongolian"!
What?
Pitch black!
Hello!
Oh, there it is!
I can see it!
It's on top of the pudding!
Oh, that looks so good!
Homemade pudding on top, which one do you want?
Oh, wow!
What do you want?
I want something different for each of us, Centrair.
Hey!
I've got a month left on this.
Oh, you'll get to see it, won't you? Here.
I'm going to try to play it back, right?
I'm doing this fresh-squeezed stuff.
I've never had it before.
Pudding!
Pudding looks so delicious!
Next, the whipped cream is stowed away.
Fresh cream here?
Wow!
Wow! The whipped cream looks different!
Beautiful.
It's like each one is its own mon grandson.
What?
Yes, each one.
It's wonderful.
While still being rustic.
Wow!
Genius.
Oh no, it's beautiful.
It smells like a flip-flop.
oh my goodness oh my goodness oh my goodness
thank you so much!
Pudding?
This is it!
It's "Buke Yashiki Mont Blanc"!
Not bad!
Then... two black ones.
Takeyashiki Montblanc!
Yes!
Bon appétit!
Mmm! How is it? How is it?
Yum!
Mont Blanc!
Looks so good!
It may not look like it, but it tastes like Mont Blanc.
The pudding tastes so good!
Pudding is sweet!
First comes the sweet pudding.
But then the chestnuts come in!
Delicious!
So rich!
Then I'll have a squeeze of this one too!
Yay!
It's amazing!
Because I just made this.
I'm off!
Bon appétit!
Bye!
Mmm!
How is it?
Chunky!
Chunky?
It's a different samurai residence.
Maybe not.
The chestnut flavor is very strong.
More chestnut flavor.
You can feel it?
Yes!
No! Delicious!
Spring from Yujiki
presented by Yuuji
The moment you put it in, you can smell the fragrance.
I walked down that street in Buke Yashiki.
The blackness.
It's strange that you're eating it, but I'm glad you're enjoying it.
You should definitely come.
It's stylish.
It's got a little bit of a Japanese feel to it.
The entrance is really nice.
It's like a camon.
Thank you for the food!
In the city of Akita
There is a food entertainment where you can enjoy all of Akita
What's that?
It's here!
Akita Nagaya Bar!
You can enjoy everything here!
What is this wonderful music?
Looks like so much fun!
I'll be right behind you Haru!
Yamaage
I'll be there as soon as possible
Let's go eat something delicious
Let's go
I've ordered
There are so many dishes on the menu!
I came from Nagoya this time.
Can you tell me what Akita's specialties are that I must try?
What is it?
Well, at this time of the year, you can't go wrong with hatahata (grouper).
Hatahata-hata!
Either grilled or cooked in a pot.
Tsuru nabe (one-pot dish with cranes)
I'd like to try grilled fish
Not this one.
Maybe this one
Hatahata
I still don't want to eat rice
I want to eat it!
It's Akita, after all.
We want to eat rice, don't we?
But Akita is famous for Kiritanpo (steamed pork dumplings)
That's right.
I want to go there, but I'm curious about something... kiritanpo miso dengaku!
I want to eat it! It's absolutely delicious!
You can feel Nagoya!
Miso Dengaku
It's a bastard of a hand!
Sukiyaki flavored Hachimantai pork
The appetizer of the oshibiyaki?
It was cold today, so it stings!
It definitely stings!
Here's the sukiyaki as an appetizer.
I'll eat it when it starts to simmer.
I'll eat it.
Okay, everyone, I'm bored.
I've been in so many places today, I've taken in so much happiness through my eyes, mouth, and body.
I'm tired of it. Please eat it while thinking "I love it.
Here's to you, sparkling toast!
Cheers!
There's some kind of explanation here.
Chopstick rest is
Akita maker's corn!
This is where the chopsticks are.
Isn't this it?
It's a chopstick rest, but you can eat it!
Let's eat!
Bon appétit!
He's so cool!
It's so sweet!
It's so good!
Here it comes.
Oh, wow.
Wow.
Oh, man.
The aroma is so good!
This is the appetizer.
I forgot.
It's just one bite too many, right?
Like this.
I see what you mean.
This pickled cod roe is incluy...
This is mine.
Like that.
like this
from memory
Clients
Oh my God.
This is the place.
Eggs!
Thank you very much.
I'll have some.
Nice face.
It's delicious.
Is the meat sweet? The meat is sweet?
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm a dipping and eating kind of girl.
Mmmm!
How is it?
It's good!
It's so good!
Is it this good?
Did we only have to go through it once?
Don't you have to go through it several times?
I'm going to pour the rest of the broth over the rice.
I know, right?
I'm going to pour it over the rice.
I want to pour it over the rice.
What's that?
I see a pot.
The kettle, isn't that bean dip? What's that?
What's that? Is that rice?
Yokote City is represented by Kamakura.
Kamakura.
Every year, there is a festival held on the 15th and 16th of February.
It's already a winter tradition.
Here at the Kamakura Pavilion, you can experience the world of -10 degrees Celsius all year round.
Minus 10 degrees Celsius?
Can you imagine? Minus 10 degrees Celsius!
Right!
The museum is open!
Oh, there is an entrance right away!
Experience Kamakura at minus 10 degrees Celsius!
Yay!
Here it is!
Hey!
It's so cute!
What?
Team president, this post.
It's from Yu Takahashi's festival.
That was the year we performed.
This is it?
It's Akita by nightfall.
It's a child.
Let's go in.
Oh, wow!
It's like an inversion.
You know, you actually have to change.
Can I wear this?
Let's all get dressed together.
Oh, wow! That's nice. It's like Kamakura.
Okay, I'm going to change now.
How do you like it?
By the way, Killer Whale.
The canal version.
Canal.
What a surprise.
Rare!
It's cold!
It's so cold!
It's so cold in Akita.
Hey, hey, hey, hey...
I've seen it!
me
Oh, no! Kim Sha-chi inka makura!
You guys have never done anything like this before, right?
I want to try it and see if it really freezes.
I've got some cash register towels for you.
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on.
It's too surreal.
me, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang...
the sound of a rupture will stay in your ears and the sound of a rupture will stay in your brain.
I'll give it to you
aer ame it's a righteous woman!
Boo-boo, that's cold!
hey or someone is getting... wait what's going on... we just got a cold... we're not freezing...
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Well, maybe it would be different if there was a breeze or something outside.
I'm not sure if it would be any different if there was a breeze outside, or if it was a cold.
I'm not sure if you know the results of the study, but I haven't done it yet.
Third place, servers!
Akita, come on, Zsa Zsa, do you guys like a good belly school?
No! I heard that the skill-building school is thriving!
I've been made by a girl who knows what Ibri Ibri Ibri Epakari Ibri is!
I'm in the mood
I can already see that you're in the right mood... and I'm not just saying that you're in the right place.
Here we are, ladies and gentlemen.
Hello, there you are. Nice to meet you.
I'm from Nagoya.
I love gakko too.
I love gakko.
Gandhi, I cried with it.
I'm just a little bit
4Yeba Yama Boo Boo Iblee is working!
99itudes patty
bouvet ku pirate ne
команodate The nameplate quet in this is Amber has the species that reminds you of handmade, people who kept her mackaman, married, and did something just like this. Amber has the species that reminds you of handmade, people who kept her mackaman, married, and did something just like this.
That degree is Akita sake from Centria
Gakko Gakko
Mr. Sato, what is this hut here?
The one I just saw was the second day over the Ibushi.
This is the shed where they put in the firewood this morning around 11:00 a.m.
In the morning!
Not yet!
Daikon radish!
Still radishes.
I feel like I'm the one sweating.
Home.
Smoke!
Oh, my God!
You're sweating.
I'm sweating!
I didn't know it was that different.
It's totally different.
It's more in my stomach.
Yay! I'm so happy!
Iburi school!
School!
This is actually made by Mr. Sato
Yes, that's right.
This is the picture I made.
Wow!
I could use it!
It's really big!
Mr. Sato's Iburi school!
Yay! Nice aroma! Bon appétit!
Mmm! Nice texture!
There's another one!
Cheese is good too!
What's that?
Is that cream cheese?
It's different with cream again, isn't it?
Hey! I'm glad it's done!
The cheese is mellower, but it's got a little bit of a smoky feel to it.
Hey! Yes!
It mellows it out! Yummy!
Yum!
I made it myself.
Is this your favorite way to eat it?
What is it?
Kimchi kimchi!
Hey! Sounds delicious!
I can't wait!
Nooooo!
At first, it's kimchi in your mouth, but the more you chew, the sweeter it gets.
The more you bite into it, the sweeter it gets.
Mmmm...
I'm so happy.
It's delicious.
You should definitely try this.
I want you to eat it.
I didn't know there was such a way to eat it.
Then, Mr. Sato, can you tell us the Akita dialect for "Iburi gakko is the best"?
It's a company called Iburi Gakko.
It's a company called "Iburi Gakko." It's a common name here, so it's "Iburi Gakko" style.
Iburi gakko kei.
They are early.
They're all here.
I can see them.
What is it?
It's kiritanpo dengaku.
Wow.
It's huge!
Isn't it amazing?
It's amazing.
Let's have the kiritanpo dengaku with miso.
Bon appétit.
Delicious!
Miso is so rich!
The rice is here!
Now, let's open it!
Pappapa!
Shiny!
Smells great!
Yeah!
Shiny!
Absolutely delicious!
Let's try it!
First of all, nothing on it.
It's so shiny!
Bon appétit!
So sweet, so sweet, so sweet!
Sweet, sweet, sweet, sweet, sweet, sweet, sweet, sweet, sweet, sweet, sweet, sweet, sweet, sweet, sweet, sweet, sweet, sweet.
Oh, yeah, I eat that all the time.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. It's so good.
I'll get it.
It's so good.
Tender, sweet, delicious, soft.
Each one is so thick and filling.
It's so luxurious.
Delicious.
So soft and fluffy.
Oh, my God!
The soup smells so good!
It's oozing.
Delicious!
It just keeps coming!
Mmm...
Again, from Centria to Akita...
I'm sure the second half is great, but I'd like to try some sake too...
I'm sure you'll be able to find a lot of information about the company and its products.
the numbers on the side of the bar are numbers... what do they stand for?
ah, ah, ah, it's very easy to understand for reference what do you recommend?
Our first recommendation is the "heavenly toast"!
I'd like to have one type...
I'd like one more kind.
please.
Oh, please...
Yes, please.
Heh heh heh heh
I like your thumb.
I like the thumb.
Oh, my...
It's really good, and it's even better now that I've had it.
Let's sip and savor!
amaran ao 4
The rain makes it easy to see.
I'm sure you'll be able to find a way to get a good look at it.
I'll be right back.
ni kamapai chan chan
Oh, but it's easy to drink.
Yeah, but it's easy to drink.
Delicious!
I like it both ways.
I guess there are different tastes.
Since we're here, can I ask for another sake recommendation?
Sure.
Let's try Akita's popular sake.
Oh!
The Snow Bosha at the castle.
Yukinobosha
Wow, nice label!
Yes, it is!
The Snow Monks' House will be a little sweeter.
Sweeter?
Sweet.
I'm looking forward to it.
May I have some?
I'd be happy to.
So many different kinds of sake.
We can compare.
That's great!
Shall we have some?
Cheers!
Delicious!
I want something like this... the aroma in your mouth after you finish it is so good... floral, gentle, but floral...
I'll definitely try this one!
It's still pretty good, but...
I'll definitely try this one.
walli
I'm not sure why I stood up on the video, but I'm here because
I'm a little bit over it and I'm going to love it even more tomorrow!
I'll love you even more tomorrow!
I can't plant everything.
Thank you very much, Mr. Ranfeli!
Now adults are body futtei completa
Spread the word!
Thank you, fala!
Come on, omie.
Booooo!
So our trip to Akita is already over!
Hey, it's really great!
I experienced a lot of things, but since I came all the way here, I want to buy a lot of souvenirs at the airport.
Isn't that the best part?
Isn't it great? Souvenirs... lots of souvenirs in this area.
It's so beautiful.
Yuzuki and I will be here with our team.
Me and Yuzuki, we'll go shopping in the spring.
Just the two of us.
Okay, let's split up and I'll be on my way.
Shall we choose this spring?
Yes!
Yeah, it's cute!
I'll start with Akita Ichimaru.
Wow, wow, wow.
So cute!
There's all kinds of delicious food, too.
There are potato chips with smoked brussels sprouts.
I've seen these before.
That's right.
I just saw it.
It's made of "iburi goko" (pickled sweet potatoes).
Iburi gako is being made.
I'll keep an eye out for it.
Could this be...
The first thing that comes to mind when you think of Akita
Kiritanpo!
What's more, it's a cup of soup!
Amazing!
So cute!
I like it!
I'm lost
I'm so lost!
I can't decide at all.
I can't decide.
This was also on the big vision screen right after getting off at Usa Airport.
It seems to be the most famous souvenir of Akita!
I'll have to get this one!
One?
I'm curious about more!
But you know what, let's just pick one.
One of each.
Okay, okay.
What shall we do?
Okay, now let's see what we've got for souvenirs.
What's that?
It's so cute!
Iburi goko (pickled smelt) T-shirt!
That's cute!
It's cute!
It's possible.
Mark
Ayuzuki, this is...
Akita dog hat.
It's cute!
But... there's a bald guy too.
She looks like a mom.
She's like a bald mama.
I don't know you.
I think she likes Yuzuki.
I was just watching this.
You seem to like yuzuki so much!
They eat it on bread!
Mark
There are too many things to mark
What should I do?
Isn't this the kiritanpo zone?
Wait, this is bad!
Kiritanpo cup soup!
Isn't this bad?
It's amazing!
Wait, there are so many kinds.
Selfie soy sauce!
Yuzuki, have you decided?
I'm really torn... but I'm thinking about an iburi gakko T-shirt.
Right?
Yeah.
Have you picked out your souvenirs?
I did!
Let's start with the unveiling.
I'm curious what you chose.
I'm curious.
Well then, Haru...
Haruka!
I'm here.
What's that?
Kim Man
The number one souvenir!
The one you'll definitely see!
I chose this one because it looks delicious!
Want to go, Ho-chan?
I got a stuffed Akita dog.
So cute!
It's so cute!
I'm going to do this when I meet her.
I'm Hanako!
He's so cute!
So cute!
What's up?
You're a dashi-maker.
That's right.
And what's that?
I'm so confused!
I wanted to get this as a souvenir for sure.
It's called Kiritanpo Cup Soup.
It's this size so you can enjoy Kiritanpo.
It's great!
I love it!
And I'm going to buy
I'm wearing an "Iburi Goko" T-shirt!
Wow, so that's what you wear!
I took the first bite and ended up with this.
I see.
I had her marked in various ways, and I thought... this is the girl I like.
You really love your school.
You love her, don't you?
Here's an "Iburi Goko" T-shirt.
Souvenirs!
We bought a lot of souvenirs!
We've had our fill of Akita, haven't we?
Don't you want to go home?
I'm so happy to have bought so many memories and souvenirs!
It was really fun!
I thought this is what Akita is all about, just like last time...
When I think of Akita, many things come to mind, but...
But when I come here, I like it even more.
I love Akita even more when I come here.
We did a lot of things like this
I love Akita even more!
I want to come again
Lastly, let's all go together!
Seino
Soratabi from Centrair
Akita Sarkyu